How many Star Trek uniforms
do you have?
Just two:
(Leonard:)everyday and dress.
(Priya:)Uh-huh.
(Priya:)Listen, we need
to talk about something.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God, you're breaking up
with me!
(Leonard:)Why would you take me out
shopping
(Leonard:)and then break up with me?
That is so cruel!
(Priya:)Leonard, I'm not breaking up
with you.
(Leonard:)Oh, okay.
(Leonard:)So, what's up?
(Priya:)It's a little weird,
(Priya:)your ex-girlfriend hanging out
here all the time.
(Leonard:)I know.
(Leonard:)I usually never see
my ex-girlfriends,
(Leonard:)unless their hard drives crash.
(Priya:)I'm just saying, how would you
feel if I was hanging out
(Priya:)with my ex-boyfriend?
(Leonard:)Um, not great, I guess.
(Leonard:)But Penny and I are
just friends.
(Sheldon:)I don't care.
(Priya:)This is a woman you have
slept with.
(Priya:)If you want her around,
(Priya:)then I have to wonder if maybe
you're not ready to move on.